Mama!
Poor mom!
Mama...
Huh?
mama!
mama?
Poor mom
Mama, poor mama
Mama?
Mama, mama!
Poor mom
Mama, mama...
Uh, uh...
Hongyeon was sealed
It's a mark
What do you mean ‘Hongyeon’?
When a person is born
I am born with a scarlet face.
With my fate
It's a connected thread
The red lotus was sealed away.
Past relationships and memories
It'll all be gone
Those words...
After waking up
The words of someone I saw for the first time
It will become a memory of this woman
Take good care of yourself
What people have lost
I'm bound to wander around looking for it
This woman erased it with difficulty
So as not to find memories
With my lost relationship
So that we don't meet again
Be careful
As long as it was cut off once
with stronger manpower
We'll pull each other
Huh?
uh?
Mama, mama, mama
Who are you?
drowning
My memory has been lost.
your name is bakdal
I am your aunt
Not my biological aunt
Someone who was very close to me
It's family
Originally, I was a slave at a Daegat house in Hanyang.
run away at your age
Parents and children
The whole family died and you were the only one left
I survived
So never
You can't come to Hanyang
Park
moon
This
Yeseo
Stay still and wait.
There is a lot of corruption
Faces are difficult to recognize
Please check it yourself.
I don't like it
I won't do it
It's not my bin
How can I
Are you checking Amon's body?
see it right away
The abandoned Mr. Kang
Is that correct?
If I dance the sword dance
That's only
It will become a dance floor for the sitting table.
Be sure to cut off the head of the person sitting in the chair
About poverty and poverty
will take revenge
I was curious about this before.
Why is it a case of the Year of the Pig?
Of the poverty-stricken mama and the middle-aged mama
If it's for revenge
The poisoning case of Joongjeonmama
Isn't it right to dig into it?
Because I've tried it all
Because everything failed
If you find people who are even slightly related,
everyone died
I lost my poverty and thought about it every day
Where should I start to turn back?
Mama's death
Gyesanyeon incident
Queen Jangjeong's false accusation case
Where should I start from?
I realized it only after thinking about it for a long time.
The arrow fired cannot be returned.
time is like an arrow
If you can't turn it back
There is no choice but to suffocate the enemy.
Yeonguijeong Han Soo-hoon, Assistant Judge Han Chi-hwan
The Great Queen Mama’s brothers
First person to report death incident
Kim Han-cheol
After acupuncture to restore energy,
Underwear specialist Lee Dong-hyeon
On the first day of October in the Year of the Pig
Meaning of Kim Han-cheol
Recommendation by undershirt Lee Dong-hyeon
First day of September in the Year of the Pig
Atoms are microscopic
His Majesty the King passed on to Shinshi
But the time the two of you practiced wooden swords was
Oshi
The person who prepared the wooden sword at this time
Sigangwon Crown Prince
Kim Han-cheol
upper left
the beginning of absolute power
Gyesanyeon incident
degradation
Until now, you
What's going on?
I think I should use that room.
Decorate it well so that you can stay comfortably.
There is also some space for doctors to provide treatment.
I made it
I'm sorry, but for what purpose?
Do you mean to write it?
Why again did the congressman
Are you calling me here?
The original beauty
How to come out of health
Must be healthy inside
Beauty comes alive too
Oh, the master of beauty
Because I don't even know that, Won
But
Are you sure you are a competent congressman?
A real congressman
I heard they handle Dokdo well.
Sure
I guess so?
Just ask anything.
Now, if you do it, it's a hangnail
one time
alcohol, big
It is a deadly poison that kills instantly with just one sip.
No reaction to silver
The body does not rot to black
What is this poison?
Where in the world can you find such poison!
ah!
get out
hangnail
- Get out
-Handle once
- alcohol
Big
Even in one sip
- Ah...
- Get out
It's a deadly poison that will kill you instantly
get out
No reaction to silver
Get out!
The body is black...
get out
not corrupt
Get out!
This poison
What could it be?
No, oh my god, such poison...
Get out!
get out!
- degradation
- Everyone said they didn't know
Those who sometimes added
everyone said the same thing
Oh my goodness
Where can you find such poison, yes?
No, well, I don't know if it's Jim Dog.
Oh my...
Jimjo's Poison
It's Jimdog
I'm guessing one thing
Originated in ancient China
Isn't it Sangsang Joe?
The left figure takes advantage of that point.
A ghost or a legend
Anyway, it's a nonsense story
People will be more interested
It's like creating a story.
If Jimjo is real
The Qing Dynasty will have to investigate.
What you are investigating directly is
It's dangerous
We need helpers outside the palace.
I feel the same way.
not my revenge
If you think of it as my revenge
It would be better
Are you Prince Jeun from Shinju Temple?
That's right, but
Who are you?
Three characters
degradation
Thanks to the blessings of His Majesty the Lord and His Majesty,
Even though I was reinstated
ungratefully
I couldn't come see you
Please kill me
you
Do you hate me?
Don’t you hate His Majesty the Lord and his Majesty the President?
Lift your head up
I came to borrow your heart
Will you join me in my revenge?
So
What I learned from this visit to China
What is income?
At the end of the question
The man who raised luggage
I found an old man next door
According to the old man from the Qing Dynasty, he
Received a lot of money in the year of Imjin
sold the baggage
They say he boasted
Deterioration, deterioration...
In the year of Imjin, Jwa Sang Dae-gam went to the Qing Dynasty.
I once went there as a delegation.
yes
At the time, it was a military administrative decree.
There would have been no way to inspect the goods.
A monster-like creature without a sound or rumor
Could have brought it in
The old man might have something to do with it.
As soon as the message comes from the Qing
Let me know right away
The clock is mine tomorrow
Don't send someone to take it.
Didn't I tell you?
The watch is broken?
Bring it even if it's broken
'Cause I'll break it, shit, shit
Why are you doing this?
Now, the ones on the left are you and me
Don’t you know that we fought over disputes?
But if I go back empty handed
I would have lost to you
I'll think about it
But, I
won't lose
Wow, that’s pretentious.
No, but here
No matter how ghastly it is
Why is there so much fuss?
Hey, Yoon Se-dol, don’t talk back.
- Huh?
- Mr. I
This is Hongyeon!
I found my partner
Uh oh, ah, ouch
Oh my, oh my
If you leave it nicely
Are you saying your hand is broken?
Are you speaking?
What can I say
Oh, thank you, thank you
Could this be a way to run away?
That could happen, yeah
Can you even touch it?
What did you say earlier?
a sane person
Are you treating me like a ghost?
They say he’s a sane person?
kid!
Do you know this kid, brother?
‘Brother’?
He's my cousin.
But
Brother, do you know this kid...
Oh my
I missed you, ma'am.
Hey you
‘Madam’?
This...
Ah...
Oh, oh, why are you like that?
Hey!
Give me my clothes, you thief!
Oh my, I'll give it to you, I'll give it to you
I'll take off the bear bag, ying.
Mr. Ai, give it to me right away.
I'm sorry, ayu, ayu
Oh, it's cold, it's cold
Oh, it's cold, oh, it's cold, it's cold
Has your feet depended on your new badge?
where did this go
Are you looking for this?
That again
When did you take it?
I didn't tell you
Don't think about running away
Give it to me, my new badge
- You don’t like it?
- child
Why would you take that...
‘Baga Dal-i’?
Ying, Boryeong Park Gaekju
Luggage Jangsu Gumanyu
Why did you go all the way to Boryeong?
It's my hometown
Oh, Haengsu.
You are my aunt
My parents are both there too.
Did you have parents? Since when?
This again
What kind of novel sound is this?
Been there since birth
That can't be possible.
It's crazy, really.
Why someone else's birth
That's why I am suspicious, indeed.
Wow, hey
What? Oh, why is that
Put it in there...
Uh...
No...
Wow
Mom, Mom, what time is it?
Uh, it's probably a hash.
Oh, I'll just leave for a moment.
Where are you going? It’s night.
I have something important to do, uh
After this is completed well,
I got a lot of money
Even if it's not all of Nari's things
I'll do my best to compensate you somehow.
Well, I'll leave this to you and this to your luggage.
I won't run away, I'll definitely come back
Brother
I'm staying at Shinjusa Temple.
They say they've never seen Mama Poor.
Are they very similar?
Is it just that they look alike?
Same, very
Yeah?
Night and a lot of money...
This is definitely dangerous
‘Dangerous work’?
That's right, it's dangerous.
The traveler, is he outside?
yes
A widow in this town
Are there any noble women?
They say she's old man Huh's daughter.
Ah, that
It looks like Kim Ji-pyeong’s house.
Your little lady
That's Mr. Heo's wife.
Anyway, okay, let's go out and see.
yes, yes
Hey, are you fearless?
Am I ignorant?
Treating Hanyang carelessly
You shouldn't go around
What does that mean?
This damn bitch
Just get caught, really, huh?
No, why go to Hanyang, Hanyang
A slave who ran away
What kind of wealth and fame do you want to enjoy?
Are you going to Hanyang?
Oh, did you get that?
what?
My daughter Ganttaengi
The moon is like a clay pot
I leave my liver behind.
It's time to cause a major accident like this
- child
- I should have taken care of my mental head as well.
Oh my!
You left that behind too, maybe?
Oh my, really
- Nong is coming out now, Nong, huh?
- Oh my gosh
The child is surprised
Let’s go to Hanyang now, huh?
We went to Hanyang and found out
There's at least someone
We're going to die too, right?
Now, if we catch dinner
The only thing that will be cut off is the neck, oh no
Wow, I'm a crazy bitch. Who's to blame?
It's a jigpaljikkonji.
Oh my, your arms are crossed here
- Gasena, Ing
- What are you doing?
draw, draw
- Mom, oh, oh, oh
- Oh my gosh
Hmm...
At first glance, it seems
It seemed like he was a slave who ran away from Hanyang.
'Nobby'
It's probably a serious matter
I feel like I'm caught up
This is crazy, really, oh my.
But why are you going there?
Ah
Hey, I used one gamtu.
A debt collector scarier than a tiger
Well, something like that
If the poor don't die, they live
sold into government slavery
Is there any possibility?
It rots due to being left in the water for a long time.
Couldn't see the face properly
Just in case
Even if it's just one chance
You too
You couldn't protect it
Who is poor?
Would you like to protect it?
So, so, I'm sorry.
Damn, that backpacker
There is no way you are poor.
If it's really poverty-stricken
The sacred promise given by His Majesty
refused and ran away
I am a high treason criminal.
If the child is really poor
If only poverty were to survive
I grab that one hand and run away
But if that child is not poor,
Is he really just a backpacker?
If you are a slave who ran away
that child will die
So this feeling
Let’s do it with sympathy.
Well, let me ask you something.
I heard there is an oil market opening here.
Why can't you see it?
Ah, have you seen this crazy guy?
Do it now
Is it possible that the intestines are open?
Oh my, I really, really
Oh my, it's ruined
- Oh my!
- Shhh, shh, shh
I just arrived
No, why is it like this?
They close quickly.
Boy, business is ruined today.
It's ruined, it's ruined!
Hey, you too
You need to sleep
Oh, please go now, I'm busy.
I'm so happy
Huh? Where did you go?
Looks like you're busy. Please check your work.
Hey, hey, you, you, go to the temple, go to the temple
grunt
Hash Eunwolgak back alley
Come out and pretend you decided to commit suicide.
Oh!
Hmm, why, why are you like this?
I wanted to check something
Excuse me for a moment
What are you doing now...
That's right, a bangmul seller during the day.
Well, let’s take a look at the luggage on your back.
Why is my luggage, why is my luggage!
No...
Put this down
Oh, no, no, no, why...
No way
- Mistress
- No.
Oh, if you're here
How is it?
- Take this!
- I've been looking for it for a while.
Let go of this!
Ah, ah, no.
Run away!
I'll solve this somehow
Baby, it doesn't work like that.
My wife has a decided place to go...
- Ah!
- Uh...
Uh...
- Huh? Nari
- Ah!
uh
Oh my, ugh
Mr. Lee
My lord
What are you doing here?
Write, go
How are you going to deal with it all by yourself?
I worry when I have some free time
You'd better listen to me now
No...
Oh my, this is a secret.
Actually
I am the master of battle
You can trust me and go
If you do it, I'll leave it to you.
Nari, I don’t know who you are.
I don't know who you are
I will tolerate that rudeness.
My introduction is late, I am Jaune...
Huh?
Ha, uh...
Ah...
You are no longer
He tells me not to get involved in this matter.
If the Kims go to work,
Due to the political actions of the great army
may be seen
stop
Why are you doing this? Please send it to me.
If you send it to me
Where are you going?
How far can you go?
That woman is safe
Do you think you'll be okay?
Because it doesn't matter
Don't worry about it, just get out of the way.
It's already too late
Mistress!
madam!
Now everything...
It's over
No way
I can't take you
This
You too are accomplices
If something happens to Aggie
They are more than half responsible, you know?
Get the lady away
yes
Come this way, baby.
Baby, wait a minute, baby!
Let go of this! No...
I am worse than them.
They are
holding a string
I'm following my master
Because of Gangsan’s laws, I
With the same gentleman
On the other hand, I ate it.
A slave who ran away from Hanyang, right?
Who said that...
I'm trying to hide my identity
popping out
Start by correcting your Hanyang accent.
Because?
As I am now
Are you threatening me?
I don't mean to blame you.
Trying to blame
Especially not
you are very lucky
Because you met me with that face
the big money you mentioned
I will give it to you
Get out of this
Leave Hanyang immediately
Why is Nari giving money to Ji?
you are doing this now
Isn't it because of money?
-What is this...
- Eunjangdo, ‘White Book of Virtuous Women’
‘Suicide Collection’, ‘Chunhyangjeon’
- That's...
- To others
Become a virtuous woman
Encouraging self-determination
Going around selling things
The woman you know
Do you not want to die?
For merchants
Didn’t he have that level of loyalty?
Is it for camouflage?
Things like that
Why would you sell it?
‘Things like that’?
If someone wants to die, you have to stop them.
Praising the god of war
Why did you publish ‘White Paper on Virtuous Women’?
If I had a knife in my hand
Gotta stab the bad guy
Why did you cut your throat?
ha
Interpretation: If you think it’s novel,
Chunhyang, the representative virtuous woman,
What are you going to say?
Oh my, to Chunhyang again.
You're the type of person who can only see from the outside.
listen carefully
What Chunhyang protected
It's not about chastity, it's about yourself.
- Is it fun?
- Yes
In poverty, chastity
I didn't know there was this much interest.
Or what
Is it a signal?
The content was quite erotic.
Ugh, yeah
Child, in Chunhyangjeon
Is that all you see?
Hey, what do I do every day?
I feel like I'm just getting scolded, ugh.
What Chunhyang was trying to protect
It's dignity, not chastity.
Chastity is just a tool
Tools to protect your values
‘Tool’...
Even though I know I'm not a courtesan
Out of my greed, I insisted that I was a courtesan.
To Byeon Sato
A tool to protect myself
Face the harsh world
Something like armor?
the story
Where did you hear that?
What do you listen to?
That's what I thought
That can't be possible.
Ha, what about cloth things?
Do you think I have no thoughts?
lump
If you catch the falling petals
Do you know what happens?
If you catch the falling petals...
Ji told that to Nari.
Why did you have to tell me?
I'm going to leave now and see.
Baerang, a rude person like Nari,
Because I don’t want to mix up even a single word.
If I solve this problem
Will you answer me?
- Yes?
- If I solve this problem
I asked if you would give me an answer
I will receive that silent affirmation
Get treatment first.
Because that hurt is annoying
Why, why, oh my
Let go of this, what is this, why are you like this?
Oh my, let go of this, ah, why are you like this!
Ah, why, why do you treat people like burdens?
No, where are you taking me!
Oh, why are you like this, Mom?
No, the treatment is over.
Why are you blocking me, why?
Oh my, ah, I brought you there
Until Nari comes back
He told me not to go anywhere.
No, he said he was leaving.
Why do I listen to the words of strangers?
Do I have to be stranded?
Ai, that, that, that
That's none of my business
Oh, you didn't give me this money?
Oh no, money
Money is cheap
But why?
Rep. Nari Don Solchanhi
Looks like a leak, tsk
you are better than others
I ended up having to pay several times more military service.
Ah, well, well, what is that...
Mr. Lee, why me?
What, tell me?
uh?
- Uh
- Huh?
- uh?
- uh...
Ah, ugh
Hey, you guy
Just be gentle, Mr.
Thief, thief!
Where, where?
Kid...
-Where is the thief?
- That thief, over there.
Hmm
Wow
Write it
go
Just show it to me in moderation, okay?
catch
Hey, this
Ouch!
Ugh, ah
Ugh, ugh
Hey, tea
That's right
Right
- Mr. I
Ugh
Ugh, ah
- Ugh!
- Right
Ugh
Hey, come again later, hey
No, are there plum blossoms in a place like this?
Hey Mr. Lee
Ugh, ah!
Hey, this
Ugh
Hey, I’m surprised.
Hey, you guy
You know I'm here
You did that on purpose, huh?
Ugh, ah
Even with this flower
I told you not to hit me
I gave up all my beliefs
Just identify yourself
If you came in, that belief
You could have kept it
Then it's not that cool.
Oh, please open the door.
Quick, Shinwon hyung
Hey, go ahead and open it for me.
Shinwon hyung
I'm so happy
uh
Something happened!
Now, now, huh? Now, now, now, now
Now Kim Ji-pyeong is trying to receive the virtuous women’s fee.
To my daughter-in-law who is only fifteen years old
They're forcing me to commit suicide.
That's not the point!
If it gets caught
This whole town is harmed.
What are you doing?
Both taxes and corruption will increase.
How many times
That's about manipulating the ratio of virtuous women.
It's punishment
The town's rating is downgraded, huh?
- Taxes?
- Secondary role?
No, increase it?
This damn country
To him
But
What should we do when we go?
Come attack me right now
we didn't know
We came to rescue your daughter-in-law.
They are innocent and good people.
I have to show it.
Because of that guy, huh?
Are you all going to write poison together, huh?
Then it shouldn't be like this.
That damn guy
Let’s go get your feet cut right now!
- Let's go!
help me
Go, go!
As the daughter-in-law of the Kim family,
go with honor
I made a pact with the West.
I will never die following the West.
Let's meet again after a long time
Let's call it a hundred years then
A death that neither I nor you, the West, want
Who is it for?
dare
Sell my dead son's name
Are you begging for your life?
Just manipulate the will and you're done.
It's my name.
If I cut it off for you...
It won't work
Uh, okay, no.
Who is it?
uh? Nari...
Let's see
With a silver sword that slit your throat
hanging on a rope
A jailer whose throat is burning...
Write, um, skip it.
Who, who, who, who are you?
How did you get in here?
Is there anyone outside?
Now, that woman
Stop thinking about killing me.
The news is that one person has died
If I hear it in my ears
Let alone a sergeant of virtuous women
3 generations in the past
Because I won't even be able to stare
If that woman dies
you die too
-Open the door!
- who are you? who are you?
- Oh, that, that...
- Hey, in this world
No way, you bastard!
-Open the door!
- who are you? who are you?
Ugh!
That, that, that...
Hey, this...
Kim Ji-pyeong, that bad guy
It looks great, wow!
Baby
Oh my, oh my
I'm glad
Are you hurt anywhere?
Oh my, oh my
Hey, again
What have you done?
He asked me to open the door
I think there was a misunderstanding, huh?
I really think so.
If you don't chase after him and return to the palace,
I think those people are going to kill me.
Then just smile
- Are you smiling?
- Smile
It's here, here, here!
It's that kid, that kid...
Master Gamma!
What's going on?
After receiving a report of a thief
I was dispatched
No you
To receive the fee for virtuous women
Forcing your daughter-in-law to commit suicide
That Nari...
You saved me
Is that true?
Ah...
Uh, that...
Uh, that, that
That woman is right.
I witnessed the scene myself.
Ignoring the law of the land
Insulting His Majesty the Lord
Chase that criminal, hmm!
Arrest!
But who are you?
Ah, this person is the Crown Prince...
specially appointed by
You are a secret royal inspector.
Could you please show me the mapae?
Ma, ma, mapae?
Hmm...
Aren't you Shinwon?
underneath...
- Degradation!
- You are
appointed
Because it’s a secret royal inspector!
secret royal inspector, secret royal inspector
Poor...
Hmm!
If you do it, you will be fine.
I will follow your orders.
Yeah, that's right, yeah
arrest the criminal
Yes!
It's done now
Don't worry
You can't do it, you can eat it, Mr.
Will you answer now?
If you catch the falling petals
What happens?
You know what?
If you catch the falling petals
They say first love comes true
Wow
Why, why, why, why?
Why do you keep following me if you say you don’t know?
When did you say you didn't know?
Just become the person who caught the petals
Well...
So that's why you don't know
Because my business with you is over
Stop going back now
No, that...
Now there's nothing left to do, errands to do
thank you
Thank you for saving me, Aggie.
There's nothing to be thankful for
I did it for me anyway
Strictly speaking, what I saved was
It was the woman's dead father-in-law.
If you find out your wife is dead
I will wander the nine heavens for a long time.
and
I will regret it for a long time
I did this for a weak man.
Ah...
I apologize.
Nari is so
You look sad
Was it comfort?
Oh my, I
What qualifications do you have?
Nari’s sadness and me
It has something to do with martial arts, this
It matters.
Because of you, I am all the time
Because I'm in a dream
waited so long
nightmare
This also looks sad
If you do this this time
What kind of comfort will you give me?
Would you like to buy me soup?
- suddenly?
- I need to feel secure in my stomach.
Even if it hovers around, it gets hot.
It's pretty good
Nari, it’s late.
You have to go back now...
yes, buy it
Gukbap
You are
Did you solve the false yeolnyeomun case?
Even if I imitate a saint
Did you want to pay it?
Oh, no way
It must have been caught.
This may be a luxury, but
What about politics?
A crown prince who is not interested at all
What is Seonggun?
Whatever it is you get caught
Whatever you hunt and catch
If a tiger runs wild, he should be put on a leash.
Is there a tak?
Yes, did you call me?
When was the last time you sent a letter to Woohee?
Is it still not coming?
that is
Because the lady was so strong
Send the palanquin immediately.
Even if you have to drag it, bring it to me
I have to have a national wedding with the crown prince.
Hurry up and come up
If you don't come up again this time
The Great Gamma gave this new injection.
It's all ashes
You will make it
Buy all the Yeongdeok poison
What to do if you fetch water
What's the problem?
Hey, father and daughter fight
It will only revitalize the local economy...
So the national marriage
Are you planning on not taking it?
madam!
You're already full of energy, right?
Ah, alone as a ghost in a solo workshop.
Do you plan to die of old age?
- not at all
- But how long are you going to hold out?
You can marry Mistress Jeongin.
Do you think there will be?
Would you like to give it a try?
I am unwilling.
Isn’t it an object that harms people?
It's something to protect.
me towards someone
If I shoot this gun
That's to protect it.
don't use this gun
When will I
I will hold these two hands tightly
If you do it now
I have to protect it
Hey...
Bakdal!
Me, me, me, me
What are you doing!
Tusk, why is your father here?
Oh my god!
Well, soup is next.
- What?
- huh?
- Put it off until later
- What?
I'm going to leave now and see.
- What do you mean?
- hide, hide
Hide, hide?
No, it's all there now
Where are you going?
And the soup we will eat today
If you postpone it to the next time
clearly date and time
Don't you have to tell me?
Then, yeah
See you tomorrow at 5 o'clock, okay.
What, oh, Oshi?
If you come tomorrow
You can see it here, right?
- this person!
- What, what?
- What?
- I'm going to leave now!
Do you have real parents?
More to check
Are there any left?
None
If you do that, the promise for tomorrow is
please don't go out
But Shinwon-ah
Even if I touch it, it won't disappear
That's why I keep getting greedy
Wait a minute
If you don't have shame just for a moment
Why not?
Where is the leisure?
W Hanyang, Hanyang, the city with palaces
With or without thoughts?
Tusk, if something goes wrong with your father,
What am I doing alone?
Oh my
Ah, why are you saying what I say?
The guy who pooped gets angry
- Uh
- And it's a very harsh recipe.
- Oh my, that's right.
- Do you think I don’t have any luck now?
The nae-gwan, the lady-in-waiting is right in the eye
High treason criminals who escaped
Did you come to Hanyang without fear?
How did you know that?
Our lady-in-waiting, she’s the nae-gwan, huh?
- Is your aunt like that?
-What are you talking about?
My dad is like that
- Well...
-If you don’t notice that too
Am I lacking something?
The day when my father was a lie
The mustache was removed and put back on.
I take it off and put it back on and it stays there.
Tusk
The tusks are the royal yoga tuktuk.
If you look at it, it's time to pretend, huh?
Naeggwan and Sanggung
You got hit by snow and ran away at night.
Are you smart, ya? Did you see it?
My son, ah, my daughter is smart.
Oh my, really
- Is this something to applaud?
- Ouch
Hmm, well, it's something to admire.
- Ugh
- Draw it, before we see the real scenery.
You two pack your bags and go down first.
I'm like, something
I guess I'll have to do it and use it.
Oh my, where are you running, huh?
Are we the only sinners?
You are a sinner too, huh?
I was caught wandering around like that.
Do you want to live as a slave your whole life?
It's on my nose here so I don't get caught.
The years I lived erasing even the dots
What year is it, huh?
There's a way, like this
Be careful and hide like this
- Oh my!
- Draw it, leave it alone.
My face is flat and I got a slave tattoo
I guess I want to engrave it pretty.
Wow, that was flashy.
The character is me!
That's it, that's enough, huh?
If I go out, I'm not a person, Chi.
- Huh?
- Oh my!
- Wow
-What are you doing?
Go to sleep
- Uh, draw, draw.
- Now, now.
Yeah, come on.
Yes you bitch!
Draw a split toilet, why...
Woongnyeo
I have eyes but cannot see
You have a mouth but you can't spit it out
I was surprised
After
Why are you doing that?
How could I not know where you two came from?
Fu
Thank you so much
Oh my
this grace of mine
Even if I die, I won't forget it
Forget it
Forget all the bad memories
Make only good memories.
Just eat a bowl of soup
I'll come right away, huh?
Hey
Look at my daughter's distribution, eh?
I bet my life on a bowl of soup.
Wow
Ah!
What is it?
here
Nari
If it is sub-compensation
It is the top and merchants know it well.
Do you know anything about Qing Dynasty interpreters?
Oh my gosh again
Connecting Hanyang and Pyongyang
In Uiju, the third largest city in Joseon
Did you do it one bit?
Qing Dynasty trade
Isn’t it the center?
her
Do you find people too?
Ah, my mouth hurts when I talk about it.
Walking around here and there is my job.
Injury compensation has been spread all over the country.
You can think like that.
I found your usefulness
I need to write a contract, so follow me.
Hey, I have a prior contract.
I decided to eat soup with Usa Nari.
‘Eosa’?
Nari’s cousin, whom I met yesterday.
Oh, I heard you just became a secret royal inspector?
This
I guess we're not very close?
Write it, really
Grand cousin
How can I get a government job?
That's...
maternal cousin
Yii
Hey hey
Uh, hmm, yeah
Anyway, when I finish eating
come to my house
Namjeong lives alone
Why are you at home?
'alone'?
There are a lot of people, so don’t worry.
If you do
See you later
I asked my brother about my house.
If you run away again
We saw each other at the Podocheong
- Oh, oh.
- Oh my, wow.
Ouch
Ah, ah, ah, ah...
Well, look straight ahead.
Just like that
Look straight ahead!
- what?
- what!
Where are you girl
What...
Oh my
let's not talk
The ground collided
Why are you being so mean to me, Mr.
Kid...
Oh no
No, but he
They said they would come, but why didn't they come?
Something happened, didn't it?
Hey, I'm starving.
Even me
Can't we eat it first?
Are you sure?
No, for that backpacker.
I rented this entire tavern.
To me, who has served you all this day,
Do you feel like eating soup is a waste?
Are you like me?
What's different?
The years I spent with you
My loyalty to you
I am worse than that backpacker
What do you have?
I feel different, you bastard, ugh.
Mr...
'Mr'?
How
strength in the eyes
smile
Oh my, really, shit
Mr.
Oh, that guy is really no good.
That, Mr. Lee, tsk
The soup is thick with oil
Wow
From a strange man
It smells familiar.
beard once
I never grew up
manly chin
pasted
sloppy mustache
Strangely intimidated
Looks like a guy
not a man
You are like a man
Uh, no...
Oh, wait, oh, wait
Ah, why people
Oh my, my oh my
Are you dragging it like you would a dog?
- Crazy, crazy, huh?
- huh?
Wasn’t he the eunuch earlier?
It seems that way even from the owner’s perspective, huh?
Hey, it's been a while
Since you're coming to Hanyang, huh?
Even these juniors have seen it all.
Oh, so you like it, huh?
Oh, the military officer next to the inner hall, huh?
What would it be like to be a nobleman next to a military officer?
Well, usually a king or a prince...
Ah, ho
- Deterioration of the crown prince
- Shhh
Shhh, shh, shh, shh
Oh, come to think of it.
Nari was with the moon yesterday
Isn’t that the crown prince?
Hey, our owner
Just a quick glance
This is it, huh?
This
Ugh
This evening is so tactless
I even noticed this evening
You have to take care of it to survive
Oh, by the way
Where should I go to find him?
my body
I'm going to Madam Yifan's house.
My heart will always be here
Did you do the last thing you were asked to do well?
Of course
That girl who threw away the little lady
You won't be safe.
- Uh, ow!
- Oh my, aww.
Ouch, ouch
Oh, oh
Hey, get it straight.
Look and walk
- Ah!
- Uh...
Uh...
- Ah...
- Uh, sir, uh.
Ho, ho, ho
People are so messy until the end, tsk
Hey, you thief!
I found it, I found it
Hey, you thief, huh?
Hey, you thief, you thief
Ah, ah, why are you like this?
Let go of this!
- Oh, really.
- Uh, uh...
What kind of girl is so strong?
Never be a backpacker again
don't ignore
Uh, this bitch.
This bitch stole something
What are you talking about again?
Did you eat dog food for breakfast?
Even the bullshit is very sincere.
Doing it, Mr.
Well, let me see your luggage.
No, no
What are you doing now?
Ha, that's bullshit, look.
Why...
- What is this?
- That's right, you thief.
This is this thing, this plaything.
Why is this suddenly here...
There's nothing more to see
- Drag it away!
- Yes
There are still scoundrels
I'm looking for you
You should never go to Hanyang
never
Pocheong is not allowed.
Ayu, ayu, ayu, ayu
Losing is compensation for wealth.
Uh, not in Pocheong, but in Taobang.
It is correct to handle it through the Wealth Compensation Act.
It's a long sentence
Oh my gosh
There will be a lot of singing today
That's right
I'm going to cry today
Non-verbal words, question lines, unreasonable behavior
I told you to steal water.
Old man Haengsu, no.
If you have sinned, you will be rewarded.
I've never stolen.
The truth of the incident
After understanding a little more...
It's noisy
A gift certificate came out of your luggage.
How are you trying to get away with it?
- It's a good map...
- Hello
yes
Violating the Injury Compensation Code of Ethics
Make a paste of bakga dal-i.
After hitting the 30s
cut off the bottom
God wants me to cut it off
yes
What do you mean by ‘cutting the lower part of the plant’?
Elderly Haengsu
It's really unfair to lose
Not really, really
Do not
Oh my, hey, it's mom, it's mom
No cutting at the beginning
please please
- hit it very hard
- Yes
Stop!
What is this doing?
It's in long format
No matter how noble
I can't stop writing long sentences.
I'll show you if you do it
I'm an exception
How are you doing here...
Didn't I make a promise?
let's go
To eat soup
Leave Hanyang immediately on this road.
You are lowly
It's the price of having that face.
Why am I talking to you?
Should I listen?
Where are you going?
To propose marriage
Didn't you make a promise?
Are you talking about revolt now?
Hani
Make a decision
Do you trust me?
Trust me
Because you are my family too